myhousedeals.com 2018-12-22

# MyHouseDeals.com Privacy Policy

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for myhousedeals.com and REI Network, LP. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

## Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

Your information may be shared or sold in the event REI Network, LP sells the company, merges with another company, or enters into any kind of operating agreement with another company.

## Telephone Consumer Protection Act

By providing your phone number and email address, you are agreeing to receive text messages, emails, and/or calls (Even if you are previously subscribed to the do not call list) from MyHouseDeals and our network of partners and affiliates (Lenders or related professional services) and their network of service providers.

These calls might be recorded; and may be direct, auto-dialed or use pre-recorded/artificial voices.

This consent is not a requirement or condition to purchase.

Messages and data rates might apply.

## Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

## Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (800) 973-1180 or via email at[info@myhousedeals.com](mailto:info@myhousedeals.com).**
